Guide to the Deep Dish TV Records MSS.312
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Video Productions, 1982-2018; 13.5 Linear Feet in 17 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 906 MiniDV; 470 U-matic; 93 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 81 Betacam_SP; 26 Betacam; 58 DVCAM; 27 VHS; 5 Hi8; 3 audiocassettes; 1.538 Terabytes in 6,117 files
  - Rock the Boat -- Compilation Tapes, October 27-29, 1992 (Box 90, Betacam 312_0131, 312_0132, Box 105, U-matic 312_0335, 312_0336, Box 145, Minidv 312_0731)
    These tapes include "Una Historia" coordinated by Luis Valdovino and Dan Boord and "Puro Party" coordinated by Lizzie Martinez, Brett Littman, and Jim Mendiola. 312_0131 also includes a PSA.
  - Rock the Boat -- "Youth Speaks" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Youth Speaks", November 3-5, 1992 (Box 107, U-matic 312_0352, 312_0353)
    Coordinated by Viviana Acevedo and Michelle Materre for Educational Video Center (EVC)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Video Dialtone: Mailing Our Free Speech", November 3-5, 1992 (Box 107, U-matic 312_0349)
  - Rock the Boat -- Compilation Tapes, November 3-5, 1992 (Box 90, Betacam 312_0127, 312_0133, Box 107, U-matic 312_0350, 312_0351, Box 145, Minidv 312_0728)
    These tapes include "Youth Speaks" coordinated by Viviana Acevedo and Michelle Materre for Educational Video Center (EVC) and "Video Dialtone: Mailing Our Free Speech" produced by Paper Tiger TV. 312_0133 also includes a PSA.
  - Rock the Boat -- "Women of the First Nations" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Women of the First Nations", November 10-12, 1992 (Box 107, U-matic 312_0348)
    Coordinated by Suzanne Henry, Luz Guerra, and Claudia Sperber for the Women's Media Project
  - Rock the Boat -- "Two Spirits: Native Lesbians and Gays" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Two Spirits: Native Lesbians & Gays", November 10-12, 1992 (Box 140, U-matic 312_1826)
    Coordinated by Osa Hidalgo de la Riva for Royal Eagle-Bear Productions
  - Rock the Boat -- Compilation Tapes, November 10-12, 1992 (Box 89, Betacam sp 312_0121, Box 90, Betacam 312_0128, Box 106, U-matic 312_0346, Box 107, U-matic 312_0347, Box 145, Minidv 312_0727)
    These tapes include "Women of the First Nations" coordinated by Suzanne Henry, Luz Guerra, and Claudia Sperber and "Two Spirits: Native Lesbians and Gays" coordinated by Osa Hidalgo de la Riva.
  - Rock the Boat -- "Resistencia Latinoamericana" -- Production File, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Resistencia Latinoamericana", November 17-19, 1992 (Box 90, Betacam 312_0129, Box 91, Betacam 312_0137, Box 136, U-matic 312_1401, Box 139, U-matic 312_1820, Box 140, U-matic 312_1825, 312_1827, Box 145, Minidv 312_0726)
    Coordinated by Raul Ferrara Balanquet for the Latino Midwest Video Collective; Part 1: South America, Part 2: Mexico, Cuba, Colombia, Panama; 312_0129 also includes a PSA.
    U-matic tape 312_1401 was identified as moldy by the Media Preservation Unit. This item is currently isolated from other items in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Rock the Boat -- "Caribbean Voices" --Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Caribbean Voices", November 24-26, 1992 (Box 90, Betacam 312_0126, Box 91, Betacam 312_0138, Box 106, U-matic 312_0343, Box 145, Minidv 312_0725)
    Coordinated by Waldaba Stewart for the Caribbean Video Project
  - Rock the Boat -- "Political Nineties Too: A Spanish Point of View" -- Production File, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Political Nineties Too: A Spanish Point of View", December 8-10, 1992 (Box 90, Betacam 312_0130, Box 106, U-matic 312_0344, 312_0345, Box 145, Minidv 312_0723)
    Produced by Digitales Ozbeats
  - Rock the Boat -- "Protest + Education = Change" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Protest + Education = Change", December 15-17, 1992; cuid39355 (Box 107, U-matic 312_0354, Box 144, Minidv 312_0710, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_84)
    Coordinated by Kat High for Giveaway Songs
  - Rock the Boat -- "Rebuilding Our Communities: A Vision for the Future" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Rebuilding Our Communities: A Vision for the Future", December 15-17, 1992 (Box 107, U-matic 312_0356)
    Coordinated by Nilo Cayugueo, Glenn Switkes, and Jerry Pozo
  - Rock the Boat -- Compilation Tapes, December 15-17, 1992 (Box 88, Betacam sp 312_0100, 312_0101, Box 107, U-matic 312_0355, Box 145, Minidv 312_0722)
    These tapes include "Rebuilding Our Communities: A Vision for the Future" coordinated by Nilo Cayugueo, Glenn Switkes, and Jerry Pozo; and "Protest + Education = Change" coordinated by Kat High
  - Rock the Boat -- "USA On Trial: An Indictment Against 500 Years of Oppression" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rock the Boat -- "USA On Trial: An Indictment Against 500 Years of Oppression", December 22-24, 1992; cuid39356 (Box 88, Betacam sp 312_0102, 312_0103, Box 108, U-matic 312_0359, Box 145, Minidv 312_0721, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_85)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Our Sacred Land" -- Production File, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Our Sacred Land", October 20-22, 1992 (Box 106, U-matic 312_0340)
    Produced by Chris Spotted Eagle
  - Rock the Boat -- "In the Heart of Big Mountain" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Rock the Boat -- "In the Heart of Big Mountain", October 20-22, 1992 (Box 124, U-matic 312_0528, Box 145, Minidv 312_0732)
  - Rock the Boat -- Compilation Tapes, Circa 1992 (Box 91, Betacam 312_0136, Box 106, U-matic 312_0342)
    These tapes include "Our Sacred Land" produced by Chris Spotted Eagle and "In the Heart of Big Mountain" produced by Sandy Osawa
  - "The Ninth Annual International Women's Day Festival" -- Production File, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Visions of Ourselves -- "The 1990's How We See It!: 9th International Women's Day Video Festival", March 23 - April 1, 1993; cuid39357 (Box 88, Betacam sp 312_0104, 312_0106, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_101)
  - Visions of Ourselves -- "The 1990's How We See It!: 9th International Women's Day Video Festival" Parts 1 and 2, March 23-25, 1993 (Box 108, U-matic 312_0358)
  - Visions of Ourselves -- "The 1990's How We See It!: 9th International Women's Day Video Festival" Parts 3 and 4, March 30 - April 1, 1993 (Box 88, Betacam sp 312_0107, Box 145, Minidv 312_0720)
  - Visions of Ourselves -- "Breaking a Blockade," "Staking a Claim in Cyberspace," Bars Version, Circa 1993 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0019)
  - Visions of Ourselves, Circa 1993 (Box 88, Betacam sp 312_0105)
  - Visions of Ourselves -- Jewish Committee on the Middle East Distribution Agreement, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "10 Years of Struggle," "Jobs for Youth", Circa 1993 (Box 136, Vhs 312_1399)
    Means of Productions
  - L.A. Freewaves: Experimental Video from Southern California -- Production File, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - L.A. Freewaves: Experimental Video From Southern California -- "A Crack in the Sidewalk", April 13-15, 1993; cuid39360 (Box 88, Betacam sp 312_0109, Box 89, Betacam sp 312_0111, Box 108, U-matic 312_0365, 312_0366, Box 145, Minidv 312_0719, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_95)
    312_0109 also includes a PSA.
  - L.A. Freewaves: Experimental Video From Southern California -- "Fast Focus: Southern California Youth Speak Out", April 6-8, 1993 (Box 88, Betacam sp 312_0110, Box 108, U-matic 312_0357, Box 109, U-matic 312_0367, 312_0368)
  - News You Can Use -- "Facts on the Ground: Israeli Settlements in Occupied Palestine" -- Production File, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - News You Can Use -- "Facts On the Ground: Israeli Settlements in Occupied Palestine", April 20-22, 1993 (Box 108, U-matic 312_0362)
    Produced by Anata Video with the Palestine Solidarity Committee and Tami Gold
  - News You Can Use -- "Facts on the Ground: Palestinian Statehood", April 20-22, 1993 (Box 108, U-matic 312_0363, Box 145, Minidv 312_0718, 312_0791)
    Produced by Dana Dunnells, Tony Kandah, and Mark Bruzonsky for JCOME
  - News You Can Use -- "Facts On the Ground", April 20-22, 1993 (Box 88, Betacam sp 312_0108, Box 108, U-matic 312_0364, Box 141, Betacam sp 312_1840)
    These tapes include both "Israeli Settlements in Occupied Palestine" produced by Anata Video and "Palestinian Statehood" produced by Dana Dunnells, Tony Kandah and Mark Bruzonsky for JCOME. 312_1840 also includes a PSA.
  - News You Can Use -- "We Dare to Speak", April 27-29, 1993 (Box 108, U-matic 312_0361, Box 142, U-matic 312_1843, 312_1844, Box 143, Minidv 312_0656, Box 145, Minidv 312_0748)
    Produced by Marguerite Arnold and Dialogue Productions
  - News You Can Use -- "Sacred Lies, Civil Truths" -- Production File, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - News You Can Use -- "Sacred Lies, Civil Truths", May 4-6, 1993; cuid39361 (Box 88, U-matic 312_0099, Box 108, U-matic 312_0360, Box 109, U-matic 312_0369, Box 142, U-matic 312_1845, Box 144, Minidv 312_0711, Box 145, Minidv 312_0733, 312_0747, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_97)
    Produced by Catherine Saalfield and Cyrille Phipps for the Gay and Lesbian Emergency Media Campaign
  - News You Can Use -- Collaboration with Video News Service, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - News You Can Use -- Video News Services Compilation, May 18-20, 1993 (Box 109, U-matic 312_0373, Box 141, Betacam sp 312_1841, Box 145, Minidv 312_0750)
    These tapes include "Phambili!" and "What is a Patient." 312_1841 also includes a PSA.
  - News You Can Use -- "Savage War of Peace," "Phambili" and "What is a Patient" -- Production File, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - News You Can Use -- "A Savage War of Peace", May 10, 1993; cuid39362 (Box 109, U-matic 312_0370, 312_0371, Box 142, Betacam sp 312_1842, Box 145, Minidv 312_0739, 312_0749, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_98)
  - News You Can Use -- "Phambili! Working Women in South Africa", May 18-20, 1993; cuid39363 (Box 109, U-matic 312_0374, Box 153, Minidv 312_1308, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_96)
    Produced by Video News Service
  - News You Can Use -- "What is a Patient?", Circa May, 1993; cuid39359 (Box 84, U-matic 312_0059, Box 144, Minidv 312_0697, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_99)
  - News You Can Use -- "Staking a Claim in Cyberspace: Information Policy for the People" -- Production File, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - News You Can Use -- "Staking a Claim in Cyberspace: Information Policy for the People", June 29 - July 1, 1993 (Box 83, U-matic 312_0054, Box 110, U-matic 312_0384, Box 111, U-matic 312_0389, Box 145, Minidv 312_0766)
  - News You Can Use -- "Breaking the Blockade" -- Production File and U.S.-Cuba Friendshipment Project, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - News You Can Use -- "Breaking the Blockade", June 29 - July 1, 1993 (Box 111, U-matic 312_0387, 312_0388)
    Produced by Waldaba Stewart, May Ying Welsh, and Ric Jungers
  - News You Can Use -- Compilation Tape, June 29 - July 1, 1993 (Box 110, U-matic 312_0385)
    This tape includes "Breaking the Blockade" produced by Waldaba Stewart, May Ying Welsh, and Ric Jungers; "Staking a Claim in Cyberspace" produced by Paper Tiger TV
  - Democracy in Communications -- Production File, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Democracy in Communications -- "Not MTV: Music Videos with a Message", May 25-27, 1993 (Box 109, U-matic 312_0372)
  - Democracy in Communications -- "My Sin is Loving You", May 25-27, 1993; cuid39364 (Box 109, U-matic 312_0376, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_91)
    Produced by Esther Duran
  - Democracy in Communications -- Compilation Tape, Circa 1993 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0022, Box 144, Minidv 312_0689)
    These tapes include "Not MTV: Music Videos With A Message" and "My Sin is Loving You"
  - Democracy in Communications -- "Border Crossings", June 15-17, 1993; cuid39366 (Box 110, U-matic 312_0382, Box 144, Minidv 312_0693, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_90)
    "Work in Progress" produced by Luis Valdovino; "Esperanza" produced by Sylvia Morales
  - Democracy in Communications -- "The Electronic Arrow: How Indians Use Video", June 15-17, 1993; cuid39365 (Box 110, U-matic 312_0380, Box 143, Minidv 312_0651, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_92)
    "The Spirit of TV" produced by Vincent Carelli; "Making Waves" produced by Karen Ranucci
  - Democracy in Communications -- Compilation Tapes, June 15-17, 1993 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0023, Box 86, Betacam sp 312_0087, Box 143, Minidv 312_0652)
    These tapes include "Border Crossings" and "The Electronic Arrow: How Indians Use Video"; 312_0023 also includes a PSA.
  - Democracy in Communications -- "Mirage", June 22-24, 1993 (Box 110, U-matic 312_0383)
    "The Spirit of TV" produced by Juan Carlos Maneglia; "Even Queen Isabel Dances the Danson" produced by Luis Felipe Bernaza
  - Democracy in Communications -- Compilation Tapes, June 22-24, 1993 (Box 86, Betacam sp 312_0085, Box 110, U-matic 312_0386, Box 143, Minidv 312_0650)
    These tapes include "Mirage" and "Camino de las Almas (Path of the Souls)."
  - Democracy in Communications -- "Elvia: The Fight for Land and Liberty", June 1-3, 1993 (Box 110, U-matic 312_0379)
    Produced by Laura Rodriguez and Rick Tejada Flores
  - Democracy in Communications -- Compilation Tapes, June 1-3, 1993 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0020, Box 109, U-matic 312_0375, Box 110, U-matic 312_0377, Box 144, Minidv 312_0688)
    These tapes include "A Different Vision,=" and "Elvia: The Fight for Land and Liberty" produced by Laura Rodriguez and Rick Tejada Flores. 312_0020 also includes a PSA.
  - Democracy in Communications -- "Latino Youth in the U.S.A.", June 8-10, 1993 (Box 110, U-matic 312_0378)
    "The Bike" produced by Gary Soto; "Between Friends" produced by Severo Perez
  - Democracy in Communications -- "The Debt Game", Circa June, 1993; cuid39358 (Box 110, U-matic 312_0381, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_93)
  - Democracy in Communications -- Compilation Tapes, Circa 1993 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0014, 312_0017, Box 144, Minidv 312_0692)
    These tapes inlude "Latino Youth in the U.S.A." and "Debt Game"
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Dishwarmer", September 24-26, 1991 (Box 120, U-matic 312_0486, Box 143, Minidv 312_0617)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Draft Program Proposals and Notes, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9, 10)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Funding Proposals, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Outreach Strategy and Contact Lists, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 2, 3)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Production File, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 4, 5, 6)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- PBS and Access Outreach, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Series Opening Animation Production File, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Series Open, 1994 (Box 120, U-matic 312_0489)
    Produced by Adriene Jenik, music by Blue Verhey
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "National Health Emergency: An Activist Survey", May 19, 1994 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0015, Box 84, U-matic 312_0062, Box 112, U-matic 312_0397, Box 143, Minidv 312_0618)
    Produced by Cindy Nelson
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "High Tech Baby Making: North and South", May 30 - June 7, 1994 (Box 84, U-matic 312_0061, Box 125, Betacam sp 312_0539)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Lesbian Health" Compilation Tapes, June 2, 1994 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0021, Box 81, Betacam sp 312_0025, Box 111, U-matic 312_0392, 312_0393, Box 143, Minidv 312_0620)
    These tapes include "Lesbian Health Heroes: Bringing Healthcare to the San Diego Lesbian Community" produced by Bringing Healthcare; "Lesbian Health News" produced by DYKE T.V.; and "High Tech Baby Making: North and South" produced by Kathy High and Harriet Hirshorn
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Lesbian Health Heroes: Bringing Health Care to the San Diego Lesbian Community" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Lesbian Health Heroes: Bringing Health Care to the San Diego Lesbian Community", June, 1994 (Box 111, U-matic 312_0391, 312_0395,)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Lesbian Health News" -- Production File, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Lesbian Health News", June 7, 1994 (Box 83, U-matic 312_0056)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Casa Primavera" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Casa Primavera", May 31, 1994 (Box 83, U-matic 312_0053, Box 112, U-matic 312_0400)
    Produced by Roberto Arevalo
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Compilation Tapes, June 9, 1994 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0024, Box 111, U-matic 312_0390, Box 143, Minidv 312_0622)
    These tapes include "Doing What it Takes: Black Folks Getting and Staying Healthy" produced by Donna Golden of Not Channel Zero, and "Casa Primavera" coordinated by Roberto Arevalo in collaboration with Somerville Community Access Television (Spring 1994 series)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Doing What It Takes: Black Folks Getting and Staying Healthy" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Doing What It Takes: Black Folks Getting and Staying Healthy", June 14, 1994 (Box 112, U-matic 312_0401)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Healers: Holistic Healthcare for Women of Color" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Healers: Holistic Health Care for Women of Color", Circa 1994 (Box 111, U-matic 312_0394)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Who's in Control?" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Compilation Tapes, May 26, 1994 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0016, Box 111, U-matic 312_0396, Box 143, Minidv 312_0619)
    These tapes include "Healers: Holistic Health Care for Women of Color" coordinated by Debra J. Robinson, "Who's in Control" coordinated by Portia Cobb, and "WATTS Health Project"
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "He Wo Un Poh: Recovery in Native America" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "He Wo Un Poh: Recovery in Native America", July 7-8, 1994 (Box 80, Betacam sp 312_0018, Box 83, U-matic 312_0055, Box 113, U-matic 312_0409, 312_0412, Box 143, Minidv 312_0625)
    Produced by Beverly Singer
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "(Mis)Treating Prisoners: Healthcare Behind Bars" -- Production File, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "(Mis) Treating Prisoners: Health Care Behind Bars", June 16, 1994; cuid39368 (Box 112, U-matic 312_0402, 312_0403, Box 144, Minidv 312_0699, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_106)
    Produced by Women in the Director's Chair Collective
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Compilation Tapes, June 16, 1994 (Box 86, Betacam sp 312_0086, Box 112, U-matic 312_0399, 312_0404, Box 143, Minidv 312_0621)
    These tapes include "Glass Jaw" produced by Michael O'Reilly, "The Unfinished Symphony" produced by Julie Puzon, and "(Mis) Treating Prisoners" produced by Women in the Director's Chair Collective.
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Glass Jaw" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Glass Jaw", June 17, 1994 (Box 84, U-matic 312_0058)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Toxic Wars: Community Health and Environmental Justice", November 19, 1996; cuid39377 (Box 113, U-matic 312_0413, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_107)
    An alternative title for this program is "Toxic Wars: Pollution Knows No Borders"
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Compilation Tapes, June 23, 1994 (Box 86, Betacam sp 312_0082, Box 113, U-matic 312_0414, Box 143, Minidv 312_0623, Box 144, Minidv 312_0715)
    These tapes include "Breathless" produced by Paper Tiger TV and "Toxic Wars: Community Health and Environmental Justice" produced by Miriam Greenburg and Cathy Scott.
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Breathless" -- Production File, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Breathless", June 27, 1994; cuid39369 (Box 178, U-matic 312_0199, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_102)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "The Unfinished Symphony," "Chairs," and "The Reconstruction" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Chairs", 1994; cuid39432 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_103)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "A Cry for Freedom and Democracy", 1994; cuid39433 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_104)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Compilation Tapes, June 30, 1994 (Box 86, Betacam sp 312_0083, Box 113, U-matic 312_0411, Box 143, Minidv 312_0624, Box 145, Minidv 312_0765)
    These tapes include "A Shortness of Breath" produced by Ann A. Kaneko (Los Angeles, CA); "Chairs" Produced by Julie Puzon (La Jolla, CA); "Reunion" produced by AIDSFILMS (New York, NY); and "The Reconstruction."
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "A Shortness of Breath" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "A Shortness of Breath", July 11, 1994 (Box 113, U-matic 312_0410)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Reunion" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Reunion", July 11, 1994 (Box 84, U-matic 312_0060)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- Compilation Tapes, July 14, 1994 (Box 79, Betacam sp 312_0011, Box 113, U-matic 312_0407, Box 143, Minidv 312_0628)
    These tapes include "Women of Substance" produced by Rory Kennedy and Robin Smith (Wash, D.C.); "Crack Clouds over Hell's Kitchen" produced by Educational Video Center (New York, NY); and "Report from Chiapas" produced by Cheche Martinez (Chiapas, Mexico).
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Women of Substance" -- Production File, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Women of Substance", July 20, 1994; cuid39370 (Box 84, U-matic 312_0057, Box 125, Betacam sp 312_0538, Box 144, Minidv 312_0701, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_108)
    From Video/Action Fund
  - Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired -- "Crack Clouds Over Hell's Kitchen" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - News You Can Use -- "Flying South: A Story in Video by Felipe Paz" -- Production File, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - News You Can Use -- "A Cry for Freedom and Democracy", July 20, 1994 (Box 83, U-matic 312_0052)
  - News You Can Use -- "Flying South: A Story in Video by Felipe Paz", Circa July, 1994; cuid39367 (Box 113, U-matic 312_0408, Box 144, Minidv 312_0706, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_105)
  - News You Can Use -- "NetRoots: Cultivating the Digital Park" -- Production File, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - News You Can Use -- "NetRoots: Cultivating the Digital Park", July 22, 1994 (Box 115, U-matic 312_0429)
  - News You Can Use -- Compilation Tapes, July 21, 1994 (Box 79, Betacam sp 312_0012, Box 132, U-matic 312_0978, Box 143, Minidv 312_0626, 312_0627)